<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on M365HowTos</title>
    <link>https://M365HowTos.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on M365HowTos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 01:32:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://M365HowTos.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bulk update Display Names for Teams</title>
      <link>https://M365HowTos.com/posts/Bulk-update-Display-Names-for-Teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 01:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://M365HowTos.com/posts/Bulk-update-Display-Names-for-Teams/</guid>
      <description>Set-Team cmdlet allows you to update properties of a team, including its displayname, description, and team-specific settings. Here is an example using powershell to bulk update display names for Microsoft Teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SharePoint Online Language IDs</title>
      <link>https://M365HowTos.com/posts/SharePoint-Online-Language-IDs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 01:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://M365HowTos.com/posts/SharePoint-Online-Language-IDs/</guid>
      <description>SharePoint Online Language ID is a unique identifier that represents a language used in SharePoint Online. Each language has its own ID that is used to indicate the language of the content stored in SharePoint Online. Language IDs are used to ensure that content is displayed correctly in the correct language in SharePoint Online sites and pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SharePoint Site Template ID</title>
      <link>https://M365HowTos.com/posts/SharePoint-Site-Template-ID/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://M365HowTos.com/posts/SharePoint-Site-Template-ID/</guid>
      <description>A SharePoint site template ID is the unique identifier for each SharePoint site template. It is typically a string that can be accessed through the SharePoint object model or by using the site template gallery in the SharePoint admin center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SharePoint Online Site Design</title>
      <link>https://M365HowTos.com/posts/SharePoint-Online-Site-Design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 23:10:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://M365HowTos.com/posts/SharePoint-Online-Site-Design/</guid>
      <description>Site design refers to the process of customizing and branding the appearance and functionality of SharePoint Online sites to meet specific business needs. This involves creating a design template that can be applied to new or existing sites, which can include custom themes, layouts, and functionality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SharePoint Online Site Script</title>
      <link>https://M365HowTos.com/posts/SharePoint-Online-Site-Scripts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 23:06:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://M365HowTos.com/posts/SharePoint-Online-Site-Scripts/</guid>
      <description>SharePoint Site Script is a JSON file used to define custom configurations within a SharePoint Online site. It can include a series of actions, such as creating columns, creating lists, setting site themes, etc., which can be automatically applied to a SharePoint site to ensure it adheres to specific standards and requirements. Site Scripts are reusable scripts that can be shared and reused across multiple SharePoint sites.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
